

Paweł Lorencowicz

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

During last three years I worked in the design center contributing to big international projects. Utilising good communication skills, I maintained successful working relationships with both internal and external staff. As a highly-motivated and results orientated I am looking to secure a position, where I can develop current skillset further.

CONTACT ME

- +48 725 200 007
- ☑ p.lorencowicz@gmail.com
- Warszawa, Poland
- github.com/lor3k
- in linkedin.com/in/plorencowicz

EDUCATION

- → Front-End full-time course infoShare Academy

 Nov 2017 Feb 2018
- Warsaw University of Technology Transportation and Highway Engineering 2013 – 2015
- Warsaw University of Technology Engineer's degree, Civil Engineering 2008 – 2013

EXPERIENCE

- Road Designer Assistant Multiconsult May 2015 – Sep 2017
- Road Designer Assistant
 AECOM
 Feb 2015 May 2015
- Construction Engineer STRABAG Jul 2013 – Sep 2013

SKILLS

JavaScript ES6	MacOS
React.js	Linux

HTML5 — AutoCAD

■ CSS3 ■ Photoshop

SASS Inkscape
Bootstrap MathCAD

GIT PHP

RWD **m**ySQL

LANGUAGES

English C1 German B1 Norwegian A1

HOBBIES

technologies, cycling, sailing, climbing, travelling

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z Ustawą z dnia 29.08.1997 roku o Ochronie Danych Osobowych; tekst jednolity: Dz. U. z 2002r. Nr 101, poz. 926 ze zm.).